anisearch.com 2015-06-29

# Privacy Policy

aniSearch takes the security of your personal information very seriously. Collected data will only be used within the framework of existing legislation, particularly the [Federal Data Protection Act](http://www.gesetze-im-internet.de/bdsg_1990/) and the German [Teleservices Act](http://www.gesetze-im-internet.de/tmg/). We neither sell nor share your data, unless issued to by a judicial decree. 

With your registration, you agree to our usage of your non-personal information, regarding the data processing as indicated in the data privacy statement. 

## What Personal Information does aniSearch ask for?

During registration we need you to enter a valid e-mail address, the rest is optional. You can always change your e-mail address in the control panel. 

## What does aniSearch use Cookies for?

aniSearch itself uses cookies to save various site settings that you define without having to register. For registered users with automatic login enabled, cookies also functions as a login verification.

Our advertisement partners use cookies to detect browsing behavior and adapt their ads to better match the users interests. It is not possible to backtrack this data to a person and we will not share your personal information with our advertisement partners. One exception would be if you participate in an aniSearch lottery. In this case it might be required to give your home address or your e-mail address to the advertisement partner, so they can send you the price. But in this case you will be asked for your information by us and you can decide what kind of information you want to share.

In general aniSearch will work if you have cookies disabled in your browser. For technical reasons this might hinder some of the functions, though. Most browsers are configured so they will accept cookies automatically. You can disable the saving of cookies or configure your browser to alert you whenever cookies are sent. 

!!! Delete all cookies on aniSearch.com !!!

## Forwarding Links to Other Websites

aniSearch contains links to other websites. We have no influence on those sites and cannot guarantee that the operators will abide by the data protection rules.
